Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities records, 1960-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 2: Community Development, 1960-2011; (24 boxes)
  - How Small Grants Make A Difference, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Innovation and Challenge in Community Development - A Global Agenda, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - International Guide to Indianapolis, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Interwoven Destinies, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Interwoven Destinies: Cities and the Nation, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Land of Opportunity: Columbus, Ohio, Design Charrette, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Land Use in Transition: Emerging Forces & Issues Shaping the Real Estate Environment, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Land Use in Transition: Emerging Forces & Issues Shaping the Real Estate Environment, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Leadership Conference on Conservancy and Development, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Leadership Forum on Environmental Stewardship, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Leadership Forum on Environmental Stewardship, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Leadership Forum on Environmental Stewardship, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Learning from American Cities, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Learning from Atlanta, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Learning From Baltimore, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Learning from Europe, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Learning from Europe - Remarks of Tour Participants, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Learning From Galveston, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Learning From Seattle, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Livability, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Livability City Resource Lists, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Livability Coalition Meeting, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Livability in the Intermountain West Centers, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Livability: An Achievable Advantage - Regional Conference, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Livable Cities for Florida's Future, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Livable Cities for Florida's Future, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Livable City: Revitalizing Urban Communities, Introductions, and Strategies, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Livable Communities & Aging in Place: Developing an Elder Friendly Community, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Livable Communities for All Ages, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Making Cities Livable: Lessons for the United States from Europe, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Mature Worker Retraining, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum: Building Communities Through Technology, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Metro Seattle Transit Project Report, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Metropolis Now, Getting it Right - City Image Conference Handbook and Proceedings, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Midlands County Council Planning Department: Cities in Transition, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - More Streets for People, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - National Coalition for Promoting Physical Activity Strategy Meeting Report, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood Conservation: A Source Book, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Conservation: Lessons from Three Cities, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Conservation: Lessons from Three Cities, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - New Partnership to Conserve America's Communities, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Camden Report Critique Session, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Observations of Emporia, Virginia, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Otay Ranch New Town, Urban Land Institute, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Partners and Managing Community Assets, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Partners and Social Equity, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Partners and Urban Livability: The Atlantic Community, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Partners' Green Agenda: Economics of Sustainability, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - People's Voice Heard, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia Neighborhood Initiative: Notes from community workshops in Mt. Airy and Chinatown, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Philanthropy and Economic Development, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Place Makes A Difference: Social Equity and the American Community, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Preservation and Conservation: Perspectives, Programs and Projects, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Principles of Livable Communities for All - Final Report for AARP, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for the Creation of the Bruner Prize, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for the Creation of the Bruner Prize, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Putting Families First: Managing Resources to Restore Communities, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations for the Community Conservation Section in the Final Report of the Rockefeller Task Force on Land Utilization and Urban Growth, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Reinventing Cities for People and the Planet, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Renewable American Community Conference: Local Solutions to National Problems, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Report on the Enterprise Zone: Rebuilding Urban Communities Conference, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Report on Walton County, Florida's Participation in the Shaping Growth in American Communities Program, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Report to Camden, New Jersey Concerning Partners' Visits to Camden, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Report to the Fire Department, Arlington County, Virginia, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Report to the state of Maine about the Shaping Growth in American Communities program., 1990 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Buffalo NY on parking development strategies in downtowns, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Pershing Square Management Association of Los Angeles on inner-city park development strategies, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for L. J. Cella and company on Downtown Development Organizations., 1986 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Malcolm Rivkin Associates on adaptive re-uses of old power houses, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Rivkin Associates on waterfronts, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for the City of Raleigh NC on facade improvement ordinances at the municipal level., 1987 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Retrofitting Suburbia: Making it Livable for Aging in Place - Best Practices, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Retrofitting Suburbia: Making it Livable for Aging in Place - Best Practices, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Revitalizing Communities for All Generations: Visioning a Livable Wichita Region, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Reviving the Urban Waterfront, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Rockville Development Options, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Savannah Neighborhood Action Conference: Tenants and Landlords, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Scene 2: The Reuse of Old Movie Theaters, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Selected Grants: Urban Conservation, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Seoul Town Meeting: Ways to Improve the Quality of Life, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Series of Draft Background Papers, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities, 1988-1990 - The First Two Years, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities: Report to Camden, New Jersey, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities: Report to Camden, New Jersey, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Small Seaports: Revitalization through Conserving Heritage Resources, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - South Calhoun Corridor Improvement Project, Ft. Wayne, Indiana, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Standing Tall: America's Cities, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - State of the American Community, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - State of the American Community, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - State of the American Community, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Stations and Airports: New Gates to the Cities of the Year 2000, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Planning for Economic Development: Moving Beyond the Overall Economic Development Program, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Strategies for Success: Reinventing Cities for the 21st Century, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Strategy for the Toledo, Ohio Portside Area, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Suburban Activity Centers: Tyson's Corner, Virginia, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - The Dollars and Sense of Green Business: Chambers of Commerce as the New Champions of a Green Economy, 2010 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - The Massachusetts Success Story, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - The Maturing of America: Getting Communities on Track for an Aging Population, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - The Preservation of Cultural Heritage and Cultural Property USIA Thematic Tour, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - The Return of the Livable City: Learning from America's Best, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - The Role of Transit in Creating Livable Metropolitan Communities, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - The Smithsonian Associate, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - The Use of Land: A Citizens' Policy Guide to Urban Growth, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Thinking Small: Transportation through All the Neighborhood Revitalization, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Threshold of Opportunity: Rosslyn-Ballston Mid-Course Review, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - To Save a City, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Transit Cooperative Research Program Transit-Friendly Streets, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Conference of Mayors 1996 Leadership Meeting Background Materials (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Urban Action: A New Partnership to Conserve America's Communities, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs Seminar, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Urban Conservation Areas: Their Meaning and Implementation, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Urban Edge: Where the City Meets the Sea, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Urban Horizons: A Conference on the Future of Communities, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Vending Programs: Highlights from Across America, Compilation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Vending Programs: Highlights from Across America, Compilation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Vending Programs: Highlights from Across America, Compilation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Vending Programs: Highlights from Across America, Compilation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Vending Programs: Highlights from Across America, Guide, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Walking Environment: Its Role in Urban Transportation in Boston and Older American Cities, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - What is Livability?, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - What Makes a City Livable?, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - What Makes Cities Livable: Learning From Abroad, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Winter City: A Survival Guide for the Frost Belt, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Workbook: Making a Business Improvement District for Neighborhood Improvement, Cleveland, Ohio, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Workbook: Making a Business Improvement District for Neighborhood Improvement, Cleveland, Ohio, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - World Resources: A Guide to the Global Environment, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Series 3: Culture Builds Community, 1978-2012; (24 boxes)
  Series 3, Culture Builds Community, contains the gathered resources for the long-term initiative, started in 1993.
  - A Creative Industries Strategy for Calhoun County, Michigan, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - A National How-to Forum for Asset-Based Community Development in Latino Communities, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - A portfolio on Culture Builds Community, a national demonstration sponsored by Citibank, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - A portfolio on Culture Builds Community, a national demonstration sponsored by Citibank, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Amenities: An Enticement to Tenant Action and Public Housing, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - American Libraries, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Annual Recreation Conference "Beyond the Boundaries" Forging Futures, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Arizona: The Arts in Partnership, 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Arizona: The Arts in Partnership, 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Art of Regeneration, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Art of Work and the Work of Art, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Art Works to Build Communities, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Art Works to Build Communities, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Artists as Revitalization Agents, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - ArtPlace Arts and Culture Temporium Grant Application, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Arts and Culture as Assets for Community Building: A Community Workbook, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Culture as Assets for Community Building: A Community Workbook, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Arts and Culture as Assets for Community Building: A Community Workbook, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Arts and Culture as Tools for Asset-Based Community Development, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Culture: Before School, In School, After School, Beyond School, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Smart Growth: The Role of Arts in Placemaking, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Arts as a Community Building Tool, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Arts Organizations and Public Health: Developing Relationships and Programs to Address Local Health Priorities, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Arts, Culture and Community: Building Bridges for Equity, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Arts, Culture and Entertainment Roundtable, St. Paul, Minnesota, June 10, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - ArtShow: Youth and Community Development, 2000, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Assets for a Competitive Region, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Attucks School Charrette, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Attucks School Charrette in Kansas City: Partners Report, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Attucks School Charrette in Kansas City: Partners Report, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Bejing Academy of Social Sciences: Community Development Abroad: Theory and Practice, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Best Practices for the Community Art Fund: A Collection of Examples from Local and National Organizations, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Best Practices on Culture and Economic Development, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Bridges to Understanding Children's Museums, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Building a Caring Community Manual, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Building a Caring Community: Delivering Social Services to Children At Risk Through Urban and Recreation Programs, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Building a Caring Community: Delivering Social Services to Children At Risk Through Urban and Recreation Programs, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Building A Field: The Artists in Youth and Community Development Conference, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Building a Field: The Arts Professional in Youth and Community Development Conference, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Building a Field: The Arts Professional in Youth and Community Development Conference, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Building a Field: The Professional Artist Youth and Community Development Final Report, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Building By Design, Illinois Arts Council: Arts Build Illinois, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Building By Design, Illinois Arts Council: Arts Build Illinois, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Building By Design, Illinois Arts Council: Arts Build Illinois, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Building Community: Putting the Art in Partnership, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Building Livable Communities: Creating a Common Agenda, 2010 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Business Arts Quarterly, April 1998 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Business Arts Quarterly, January 1999 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Business Arts Quarterly, September 1997 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Camden Redevelopment Agency Report: Culture Builds Camden, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Botanic Garden: Horizons for the Future Service to the Greater Chicago Community Initiative, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Botanic Garden: Horizons for the Future Service to the Greater Chicago Community Initiative, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Cultural Plan Summary, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Churches: Symbols of Community, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Coming Up Taller, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Coming Up Taller Awards, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Coming Up Taller Awards, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Commitment to Culture, Stone Soup Magazine, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Communities and Their Museums: Creating a Local Agenda, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Communities in Transition: Institutions as Fulcrums for Change, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Community Arts Fund Greater Kansas City Community Foundation, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Community Arts Fund Best Practices, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Community Arts Fund, Guidelines of the Greater Kansas City Community Foundation, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Community Partners: Museums in the Social and Economic Life of the City, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Community Partners: Museums in the Social and Economic Life of the City, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Connections Newsletter: Complete Set, 1997 - 2000 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Connections: News from the Culture Builds Community Initiative, Fall 1997 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Connections: News from the Culture Builds Community Initiative, Spring 1998 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Connections: News from the Culture Builds Community Initiative, Summer 1999 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Connections: News from the Culture Builds Community Initiative, Winter 2001 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Consultants Report to the Office of Community and Economic Development; West Valley Center, Utah, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Contra Costa County Public Library: A Community Vision for a New Central Library, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Creating Cultural Partnerships for Building Florida's Future, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Creative Approaches to Economic Research, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Collaborative Jamaica, Member Survey Binder, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Collaborative Jamaica, Report on a Strategic Retreat, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Cultural Planning at 30, Past, Present, and Future for Partners for Livable Communities, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Planning at 30, Past, Present, and Future for Partners for Livable Communities, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Planning: A Resource for Civic Progress, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Cultural Planning: The Small City Challenge, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Policy: Case Studies, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Cultural Policy: City of Wanneroo, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Culture and Communities: The Arts in the Life of American Cities, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Culture and Communities: The Arts in the Life of American Cities, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Culture and Communities: The Arts in the Life of American Cities, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Culture and Community: a Symbiotic Relationship for Livable Communities, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Culture as Social and Economic Development Resource: Multiple Uses for Your Community and Quality of Life, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Culture Builds Communities Community Workbook, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Culture Builds Communities Community Workbook, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Culture Builds Communities Community Workbook, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Culture Builds Communities Community Workbook, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Culture Builds Communities Pre-Conference Workbook, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Culture Builds Communities, An Initiative of the William Penn Foundation - Creating Catalysts for Change, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Culture Builds Communities: A Guide to Partnership Building and Putting Culture to Work on Social Issues, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Culture Builds Communities: A Guide to Partnership Building and Putting Culture to Work on Social Issues, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Culture Builds Communities: a National Leadership Forum at the Smithsonian Institution, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Culture Builds Communities: a National Leadership Forum at the Smithsonian Institution, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Culture Builds Communities: Assessments and Recommendations Emerging from a Retreat Convened in Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Culture Builds Communities: Best Practice Competition - Official Guides and Requirements, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Culture Builds Communities: The Power of the Arts to Strengthen Neighborhoods, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Culture Builds Community Best Practices Binder, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Culture Builds Community Best Practices Binder, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Culture Builds Community Best Practices Binder, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Culture Builds Community Evaluation Summary Report, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Culture Builds Community Package on New York City, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Culture Builds Community Package on New York City, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Culture Builds Community: Ford Foundation Meeting Workbook, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Culture Builds Community: Maximizing Your Cultural Assets in Hard Times, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Culture Builds Florida, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Culture Builds Florida Communities, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Culture Builds Florida Communities, 2011 Regional Workshop Series Powerpoint, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Culture Builds Florida Communities: A Final Report for The Florida League of Cities, 2011 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Culture Builds Florida Mayor Johnson PowerPoint, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Culture Builds Florida PowerPoint, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Culture Builds Florida: 2011 Regional Workshop Series, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Culture Builds Jamaica: An Arts Impact Study Binder, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Culture Builds Jamaica: Arts and Culture Impact Community and Economic Development, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Culture Builds Jamaica: Arts and Culture Impact Community and Economic Development, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Culture Builds Jamaica: Hearst Foundation Report, 2012 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Culture Builds Jamaica: Phase One Final Report, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Culture Builds Jamaica: Phase One Final Report, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Culture Builds Tuscaloosa - Stakeholders Meeting, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Culture Builds Tuscaloosa County-- A Visioning Process, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Culture Connects All: Rethinking Audiences in Times of Demographic Change, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Delta Culture Center in Helena, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Developing the Next Generation of Leaders in Arts, Culture, and Community Development, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Douglas Redd Fellowship: Class of 2009, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Downside Up Listening Tour: Final Report, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Shore Retreat: Transcript of Proceedings, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Eighteenth & Vine Charrette: Summary Report, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Eighteenth & Vine Charrette: Summary Report, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Eighteenth & Vine Charrette: Summary Report, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Eighteenth & Vine Charrette: Summary Report, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Eighteenth & Vine Charrette: Summary Report, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation Report by Robert H. McNulty on his trip to South Africa, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Examples of How Culture Builds Community, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Executive Summary of the Greater Jamaica Development Corporation Advisory Meeting, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Fact Sheets on Multiple Benefit Arguments from Culture Builds Community, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Final Report - Culture Builds Community Initiative in Philadelphia, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Forsyth County Public Library: A Community Vision for the Central Library, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Fostering Strong Communities through the Arts and Culture: A Local, Grounds-up Approach, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Frankfort Styles Strategic Planning Retreat, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Fulcrums of Change, Best Practices and Issues, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Gateway Arts District, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 4)